http://www.cmaauctions.com/cma/privacy-policy

Credit Management Association® Privacy Policy
Credit Management Association (“CMA”) respects the privacy of its customers, members, and those visiting its website and has adopted this privacy policy in order to highlight the importance of privacy and to acknowledge the new California Consumer Privacy Act. This policy, which discloses ways in which CMA gathers and distributes information, may change at any time. This policy also applies to the anscers.com website. Any changes will be posted on these websites within this policy.
Collected Information
CMA does not collect consumer data nor do we sell consumer or any customer data. It is CMA’s general policy to collect only such personal data as our members, customers, subscribers, event registrants and other visitors knowingly provide. CMA does not collect personal information from those merely browsing this website. Most information collected on the website is used to better enable CMA to serve its members and customers. We may also contact you regarding a website problem or other customer or member service-related issues.
Those joining CMA as members, registering for CMA events and other services and activities on this website or registering for anscers.com services provide personal information as requested for those actions. The categories of personally identifiable information collected may include names, titles, companies and their addresses, telephone numbers, fax numbers and e-mail addresses. Individuals are requested to provide similar information when they sign up by offline methods. In addition, in order to access the members-only restricted access portion of the website, members are requested to provide certain information.
CMA does not market to children and does not knowingly collect personal information from children on CMA websites.
Access
In order to use many features of CMA websites, you may be asked to create or provide a user name and pass code, which are used to determine whether you are a CMA member or customer or an anscers.com customer/subscriber, or otherwise authorized to access non-public portions of these websites.
Use of Information
CMA uses the data collected to improve its services to members and for marketing purposes which also relate to the provision of goods and services to members, customers and registrants. Member and registrant contact information is not made available to other members and registrants, except among members belonging to CMA’s industry credit groups.
CMA members, customers and event registrants and attendees will receive electronic and printed communications, including regular publications and information regarding CMA member and other events, elections, and other information related to the provision of member and customer services. Member communications are delivered as part of your CMA membership agreement.
CMA also provides limited information to third parties with which CMA does business, which may include names, titles, companies, their addresses and phone and fax numbers and/or e-mail addresses.
Usage Tracking
We may monitor how you use our websites including search terms you enter, pages visited and documents viewed. If you are a registered user, this information is stored with your registration information. It is unique-number identifiable, and is used solely for purposes of enabling us to provide you with a personalized website experience. Aggregated (not personally identifiable) forms of this data may also be used in order to help us understand areas for future research and to identify future features and functions to develop for the websites.
This data may also be used by CMA, in the aggregate, to identify appropriate customer offerings.
CMA does not track its members, customers, subscribers, event registrants or other visitors over time and across third party websites to provide targeted advertising and therefore does not respond to “do not track” signals.
CMA does not authorize other parties to collect personally identifiable information about our members’, customers’, subscribers’, event registrants’ and other visitors’ online activities over time and across different websites when they use CMA’s websites or service.
Purchases and Fulfillment
When you place an order or register for a CMA event or product/subscription, we may request additional information such as credit card number and expiration date. This information is used for confirmation and billing purposes. The contact information you provide is used to service the order. Also, when you register for an event, we may request additional information about your hotel, meal and other travel preferences. This information is used only for the specific event.
CMA uses third-party service providers such as credit card processing companies, shipping companies, mailing houses and event coordinators together with other service providers as required to satisfy customer requests.
When you register for a CMA event, we provide necessary information to hotels and to facilities hosting events. These parties are allowed to use that personal information only to provide services relevant to the event.
Updating Personal Information and Making Your Personal Information Private
CMA members and nonmembers may decline to have their information shared with non-CMA third parties.
If you are a member and/or customer of CMA, and your personal information changes, you may update it at any time. To correct or update personal information, and/or to mark your personal information private, email info@emailcma.org or, if it relates to anscers.com, log on to anscers.com and visit the My Account page.
Use of “Cookies”
“Cookies” are pieces of data that a website may send for storage by your web browser on your computer’s hard drive. When a user registers on the CMA or anscers.com website, the user is asked whether a cookie may be attached. If the user declines, the user may not have full access to the website. Registration, and attachment of a cookie, allows the website to provide more relevant information to the user. CMA does not use cookies to distribute or analyze information about the user.
Security
CMA provides its users with a secure online experience. To do this, we use a variety of security measures to maintain the safety and confidentiality of personal information about you. All user registration information is contained behind a firewall and is accessible only by CMA employees, contractors and volunteers who have signed nondisclosure agreements with CMA. The database is protected behind a firewall. If you have any questions about the security at our websites, please send an e-mail to info@emailcma.org.
Links
CMA’s websites contain links to websites not within the CMA domain. CMA is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such sites. We encourage our users to be aware of when they leave our sites and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by CMA websites.
Electronic Discussion Groups and Bulletin Boards
The website allows members to utilize electronic discussion groups and bulletin boards. Information that a user may disclose there becomes viewable to other users, and the user should therefore use discretion with respect to disclosing personal information.
Notification of Policy Changes
We will notify members and other users about material changes to our privacy policy by posting the privacy policy as changed on our websites. Thus, users of the websites may want to periodically review the policy for changes.
Contact CMA
If you have any additional questions, please contact CMA Headquarters:
PO Box 750114Las Vegas, NV  89136
Phone: 702-259-2622 Fax: 702-259-9908
Updated June 30, 2020
Credit Management Association
Credit Management Association helps credit, collection, and financial decision-makers get the information and support they need to make fast, accurate credit decisions.
Contact Us Phone: (800) 541-2622
Email: info@emailcma.org
Address: P.O. Box 7740, Burbank, CA 91510
Connect With Us
Newsletter Click here to sign up for our newsletter
Quick Links
Become a Member
Events
